mquiz_data = [
    {
        "question": "What special feature do all mammals have?",
        "choices": ["Feathers", "Hair or fur", "Scales", "Spots"],
        "answer": "Hair or fur"
    },
    {
        "question": "How do mammals control their body temperature?",
        "choices": ["By sweating", "By shivering", "By hibernating", "By being cold-blooded"],
        "answer": "By sweating"
    },
    {
        "question": "What do mammals feed their babies?",
        "choices": ["Nectar", "Seeds", "Milk", "Water"],
        "answer": "Milk"
    },
    {
        "question": "What adaptation helps mammals survive in cold places?",
        "choices": ["Thick fur", "Long necks", "Large ears", "Sharp claws"],
        "answer": "Thick fur"
    },
    {
        "question": "What habitat is known for its open grasslands and sunshine?",
        "choices": ["Forest", "Savannah", "Tundra", "Desert"],
        "answer": "Savannah"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the behavior called when mammals sleep during the winter to save energy?",
        "choices": ["Migration", "Hibernation", "Territorial marking", "Hunting"],
        "answer": "Hibernation"
    },
    {
        "question": "What do carnivorous mammals primarily eat?",
        "choices": ["Plants", "Meat", "Both plants and animals", "Insects"],
        "answer": "Meat"
    },
    {
        "question": "What do herbivorous mammals primarily eat?",
        "choices": ["Meat", "Plants", "Both plants and animals", "Insects"],
        "answer": "Plants"
    },
    {
        "question": "What do omnivorous mammals eat?",
        "choices": ["Only plants", "Only meat", "Both plants and animals", "Only insects"],
        "answer": "Both plants and animals"
    },
    {
        "question": "What important skill do young mammals learn from their parents?",
        "choices": ["Swimming", "Flying", "Climbing trees", "Hunting"],
        "answer": "Hunting"
    },

]
